[
  { "question": "pen (n)\n /pen/", "answer": "bút mực" },
  { "question": "pencil (n)\n /ˈpen.səl/", "answer": "bút chì" },
  { "question": "eraser (n)\n /ɪˈreɪ.sər/", "answer": "cục tẩy" },
  { "question": "sharpener (n)\n /ˈʃɑː.pən.ər/", "answer": "gọt bút chì" },
  { "question": "ruler (n)\n /ˈruː.lər/", "answer": "thước kẻ" },
  { "question": "compass (n)\n /ˈkʌm.pəs/", "answer": "com-pa" },
  { "question": "protractor (n)\n /prəˈtræk.tər/", "answer": "thước đo góc" },
  { "question": "notebook (n)\n /ˈnəʊt.bʊk/", "answer": "vở ghi" },
  { "question": "textbook (n)\n /ˈtekst.bʊk/", "answer": "sách giáo khoa" },
  { "question": "dictionary (n)\n /ˈdɪk.ʃən.ər.i/", "answer": "từ điển" },
  { "question": "paper (n)\n /ˈpeɪ.pər/", "answer": "giấy" },
  { "question": "sheet of paper (n)\n /ʃiːt əv ˈpeɪ.pər/", "answer": "tờ giấy" },
  { "question": "glue (n)\n /ɡluː/", "answer": "keo dán" },
  { "question": "scissors (n)\n /ˈsɪz.əz/", "answer": "cái kéo" },
  { "question": "stapler (n)\n /ˈsteɪ.plər/", "answer": "dập ghim" },
  { "question": "staple (n)\n /ˈsteɪ.pəl/", "answer": "kim bấm" },
  { "question": "school bag (n)\n /ˈskuːl bæɡ/", "answer": "cặp đi học" },
  { "question": "backpack (n)\n /ˈbæk.pæk/", "answer": "ba lô" },
  { "question": "pencil case (n)\n /ˈpen.səl keɪs/", "answer": "hộp bút" },
  { "question": "marker (n)\n /ˈmɑː.kər/", "answer": "bút dạ" },
  { "question": "highlighter (n)\n /ˈhaɪˌlaɪ.tər/", "answer": "bút nhớ dòng" },
  { "question": "chalk (n)\n /tʃɔːk/", "answer": "phấn viết" },
  { "question": "blackboard (n)\n /ˈblæk.bɔːd/", "answer": "bảng đen" },
  { "question": "whiteboard (n)\n /ˈwaɪt.bɔːd/", "answer": "bảng trắng" },
  { "question": "board eraser (n)\n /bɔːd ɪˈreɪ.sər/", "answer": "giẻ lau bảng" },
  { "question": "projector (n)\n /prəˈdʒek.tər/", "answer": "máy chiếu" },
  { "question": "computer (n)\n /kəmˈpjuː.tər/", "answer": "máy tính" },
  { "question": "laptop (n)\n /ˈlæp.tɒp/", "answer": "máy tính xách tay" },
  { "question": "printer (n)\n /ˈprɪn.tər/", "answer": "máy in" },
  { "question": "calculator (n)\n /ˈkæl.kjʊ.leɪ.tər/", "answer": "máy tính bỏ túi" },
  { "question": "school uniform (n)\n /ˈskuːl ˌjuː.nɪ.fɔːm/", "answer": "đồng phục học sinh" },
  { "question": "lunch box (n)\n /lʌntʃ bɒks/", "answer": "hộp cơm trưa" },
  { "question": "water bottle (n)\n /ˈwɔː.tər ˌbɒt.əl/", "answer": "chai nước" }
]
